

DevOps Engineer

Israel
Tel-Aviv Jaffa
osher.levi7@gmail.com
0508859406
LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/osher
-levi-49794a1ab

Hi, My name is Osher, and I am a highly motivated and goal-driven DevOps Engineer with 3+ years of experience managing large-scale production environments on public cloud providers such as GCP and AWS.

I have a core Linux OS understanding and proven experience with CI/CD pipelines for distributed production systems. I am also experienced in monitoring and logging complicated environments and have excellent English skills. Additionally, I have worked with cutting-edge technologies such as Terraform, K8S, Helm-Charts, Grafana, GitOps, and scripting languages like Bash, Go, and Python.

Professional Experience

DevOps Engineer Antidote Health, Israel | July 2022 - Present

- Designed, developed, tested, and delivered a production Kubernetes environment from scratch using DevOps methodologies.
- Utilized Helm chart of charts, build, test automation, and monitoring software and infrastructure to ensure reliability and scalability of the environment.
- Collaborated with development teams to ensure smooth integration of their applications into the Kubernetes environment.
- Conducted thorough testing and troubleshooting to identify and resolve any issues with the
 environment.
- Provided documentation and training to team members on how to use and maintain the Kubernetes environment.

Junior Devops Engineer Scopio Labs, Tel Aviv, Israel | May 2020 - July 2022

- Maintained software and hardware systems, including Linux On-premises, to ensure optimal performance and reliability.
- Managed the AWS account of the company, including IAM permission management, VMs, DBs, and more.
- Managed the full cycle of the CI/CD to ensure a smooth deployment process using Jenkins on k8s.
- Developed and maintained infrastructure as code using tools such as Ansible.
- Collaborated with development teams to review infrastructure architecture and implement new flows.
- Conducted security assessments and implemented security best practices across the infrastructure du a compliance regulation.
- Provided documentation and training to team members on how to use and maintain the systems.

Education

Full-Stack

Full-Stack Developer at John Bryce | January 2018 - January 2019

Developer

Front End, Back End, Data Base, Node, CSM.

Devops

Devops-Engineer at Docker Master | May 2019 - June 2021

Engineer

Programming language, Linux Administration, Infrastructure as code, Continuous Integration &

Delivery, Monitor software & infrastructure, and Cloud Providers.

Key Skills

Terraform, K8S, Helm-Chart, GCP/AWS, GitOps, Cloud security compliances